Register of the American Relief Administration Russian operational records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Russian Famine Relief, Office File, 1921-1923
  - Reports
    - Bowden, C. (Folder 19)
      - Hynes, J. (Folder 24)
      - Iglitzine (Folder 25)
      - Johnson, Charles (Box 420, Folder 1)
      - Kazaurov, N. (Folder 2)
      - Kelley, W. (Folder 3)
      - Kellogg (Folder 4)
      - Kinne, D. (Folder 5)
      - Kohl, P. Tracy (Folder 6)
      - Kumler, Preston (Folder 7)
      - Lange, J. (Folder 8)
      - Lonergan, T. (Folder 9)
      - Lykes, G. (Folder 10)
      - Lyman, F. (Folder 11)
      - Lyon, F. (Folder 12)
      - McCammon, F. (Folder 13)
      - McClintock, G. (Folder 14)
      - Macpherson, K. (Folder 15)
      - Miller, J. (Folder 16)
      - Mitchell, Mowat (Folder 17)
      - Morris, Charles (Folder 18)
      - Murphy, M. (Folder 19)
      - Nizinski, Henryk (Folder 20)
      - Noyes, D. (Folder 21)
      - Price, Frank (Folder 22)
      - Quinn, C. (Folder 23)
      - Ramsey, W. (Folder 24)
      - Raskin, M. (Folder 25)
        Available on microfilm reel 496
      - Renshaw, D. (Folder 26)
      - Repp, George (Folder 27)
      - Rollins, Francis (Folder 28)
      - Ryan, E. (Folder 29)
      - Saundes, S. (Folder 30)
      - Shafroth, Will (Folder 31)
      - Speaks, J. (Folder 32)
      - Stack, J. (Folder 33)
      - Stephens, F. (Folder 34)
      - Thors, John (Box 421, Folder 1)
      - Traynham, Floyd (Folder 2)
      - Turner, Van Arsdale (Folder 3)
      - Tuthill, M. (Folder 4)
      - Veil, A. (Folder 5)
      - Wagner, Jacob (Folder 6)
      - Wahren, I. (Folder 7)
      - Walker, H. (Folder 8)
      - Walsh, James (Folder 9)
      - Willoughby, Charles (Folder 10)
      - Wolfe, Henry (Folder 11)
  - Finance
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Appropriations (Folder 13)
- Russian Famine Relief, Agreements File, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 496-497
  Material re negotiations and agreements between the A.R.A. and the Soviet Union concerning the delivery of aid to groups and individuals, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - General
    - General
      - General (Folder 14-15)
      - American Red Cross (Folder 16)
      - European Relief Council (Folder 17)
      - League of Nations (Folder 18)
      - Nansen, Fridtjof (Folder 19)
      - Russian Red Cross in America - "Gum" agreement (Folder 20)
    - Latvia (Riga) (Folder 21)
    - Soviet Union
      - General (Folder 22)
      - Quaker-Soviet (Folder 23)
    - Ukraine and Belorussia (Folder 24)
  - Clothing remittances (Folder 25)
  - Customs duties (Folder 26)
  - Food packages
    - Intellectuals (Folder 27)
    - Secondary school teachers (Folder 28)
  - Food remittances (Box 422, Folder 1)
    Available on microfilm reel 497
  - Negotiations
    - General
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Summary, "American Relief Administration, Russian Negotiations, ", 1919-1921 (Folder 3)
    - Combatting agricultural pests (Folder 4)
    - Corn seisure (Folder 5)
    - Liquidation and withdrawal (Folder 6)
    - Operating funds (Folder 7)
    - Shipping (Folder 8)
  - Transportation (Folder 9)
  - Purchasing (Folder 10)
  - Repatriation (Folder 11)
- Russian Famine Relief, Appeals File, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 497-501
  Correspondence with groups and individuals in the Soviet Union seeking aid from the A.R.A., arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - General
    - General. "Gorky Appeal" (Folder 12)
    - Drafts of appeal by ARA (Folder 13)
    - Form letters (Folder 14)
  - Groups in the Soviet Union appealling for aid (Box 423)
    - General (Folder 1-4)
      Available on microfilm reel 498
    - Actors (Folder 5)
    - Agricultural workers (Folder 6)
    - Artists
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Sale of art (Folder 8)
    - Ballet dancers (Folder 9)
    - Boy scouts (Folder 10)
    - Clergy (Folder 11)
    - Disabled, deaf children - "Vera" project
      - Correspondence
        - General (Folder 12)
        - Earl, H. Renwick, Mrs. (Folder 13)
          Available on microfilm reel 499
      - Itinerary (Box 424, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda (Folder 2)
    - Educators
      - General - Correspondence with Lyman Wilbur (Folder 3)
      - Academicians (Folder 4)
      - Teachers
        - Secondary school (Folder 5)
        - Student teachers (Folder 6)
        - Teachers' Union (Folder 7)
        - Union of Workers for Public Instruction (Folder 8)
    - Electricians (Folder 9)
    - Foresters (Folder 10)
    - French citizens of Kiev (Folder 11)
    - German colonists (Folder 12)
    - Hospitals (Folder 13)
    - Intellectuals (Folder 14)
      Available on microfilm reel 500
    - Karelian workers (Folder 15)
    - Kyshtim Relief Committee (Folder 16)
    - Lawyers (Folder 17)
    - Musicians (Folder 18)
    - Muslims (Folder 19)
    - Nurses (Folder 20)
    - Opera singers and theater staff (Folder 21)
    - Physicians (Folder 22)
  - Individuals in the Soviet Union appealling for aid (Box 425)
    - A-E (Folder 1)
    - F-K (Folder 2)
    - L-P (Folder 3)
    - R-S (Folder 4)
    - T-Z (Folder 5)
      Available on microfilm reel 501
- Russian Famine Relief, Contributions and Contributors File, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 501-505
  Offers of aid from groups and individuals in the U.S., arranged alphabetically by subject and by subject or name thereunder.
  - General - Offers of aid (Box 426)
    - General (Folder 1-2)
    - Gifts in kind (Folder 3)
    - Housing (Folder 4)
    - Literature for Russia (Folder 5)
    - Merchandise, discounted for charity (Folder 6)
    - Personnel. Requests for positions in Russia (Folder 7)
    - Transportation - Shipping (Folder 8)
  - Groups and government agencies
    - General
      - General (Folder 9-11)
      - Pending (Box 427)
        - A-J (Folder 1)
        - K-Z (Folder 2)
          Available on microfilm reel 502
    - Churches (Folder 3-7)
    - Hospitals - American Woman's Hospital (Folder 8)
    - Schools (Folder 9)
    - United States. Army - Surplus (Folder 10)
    - United States. Congress - Appropriations
      - General - $20,000,000 (Folder 11)
      - Corn (Folder 12)
    - Women's Clubs
      - General (Box 428, Folder 1)
      - California (Folder 2)
      - Colorado (Folder 3)
        Available on microfilm reel 503
      - Delaware (Folder 4)
      - Florida (Folder 5)
      - Indiana (Folder 6)
      - Iowa (Folder 7)
      - Kentucky (Folder 8)
      - Maine (Folder 9)
      - Michigan (Folder 10)
      - Nebraska (Folder 11)
      - New Hampshire (Folder 12)
      - New Mexico (Box 429, Folder 1)
      - North Carolina (Folder 2)
      - Oregon (Folder 3)
      - Rhode Island (Folder 4)
      - Texas (Folder 5)
      - Utah (Folder 6)
      - Washington (Folder 7)
  - Individuals
    - General
      - General (Folder 8)
      - A-C (Folder 9)
      - D-F (Folder 10)
      - G-J (Folder 11)
      - K-M (Box 430, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 504
      - N-S (Folder 2)
      - T-Z (Folder 3)
    - Benoit, Aleksandr (Folder 4)
    - Breshko-Breshkovskaia, Ekaterina (Folder 5)
    - Dukes, Paul (Folder 6)
    - Duncan, Isadora (Folder 7)
    - Gest, Morris (Folder 8)
      Available on microfilm reel 505
    - Goriachevskii, Vladimir (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - Hibben, Paxton (Folder 2-3)
    - Pavlova, Anna (Folder 4)
    - Rachmaninov, Sergei (Folder 5)
    - Rosing, Vladimir (Folder 6)
    - Shaliapin, Fedor (Folder 7)
- Russian Famine Relief, Immigration and Evacuation File, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 505-515
  Correspondence, financial records, individual dossiers, instructions, memoranda, reports, and requests relating to emigration from the Soviet Union to the United States (Russian wives of American citizens), repatriation of American citizens, and A.R.A. aid to White Russian refugees in Constantinople, arranged alphabetically by category and by physical form thereunder.
  - General
    - Instructions concerning Russian wives of American citizens (Folder 8)
    - Requests for information and aid for immigration to the United States
      - A (Folder 9)
      - B (Folder 10)
      - C (Folder 11)
      - D-E (Folder 12)
      - F (Folder 13)
      - G-I (Box 432, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 506
      - J-K (Folder 2)
      - L (Folder 3)
      - M (Folder 4)
      - N-P (Folder 5-6)
      - R-S (Folder 7)
      - T-Z (Folder 8)
  - Repatriation of American citizens (Box 433)
    - General, 1921-1923 (Folder 1-2)
      Available on microfilm reel 507
    - Individual dossiers
      - A (Folder 3-5)
      - B (Folder 6-22)
      - C (Folder 23-29)
      - D (Box 434, Folder 1-6)
        Available on microfilm reel 508
      - E (Folder 7-10)
      - F (Folder 11-13)
      - G (Folder 14-26)
      - H (Folder 27-31)
        Available on microfilm reels 508 and 509
      - K (Box 435, Folder 1-15)
        Available on microfilm reel 509
      - L (Folder 16-23)
      - M (Folder 24-32)
      - N (Folder 33-34)
      - O (Folder 35)
      - P (Folder 36-45)
      - R (Box 436, Folder 1-11)
        Available on microfilm reel 510
      - S (Folder 12-36)
      - T (Folder 37-40)
        Available on microfilm reel 511
      - V (Box 437, Folder 1)
      - W (Folder 2-5)
      - Y (Folder 6-9)
      - Z (Folder 10-13)
    - Inquiries - Dropped
      - A-D (Folder 14)
      - E-P (Folder 15)
      - R-Z (Folder 16)
    - Liquidation file (Folder 17)
    - Passports (Folder 18)
    - Reports (Folder 19)
  - Russian refugees in Constantinople (Box 438)
    - General
      - American National Committee of the Red Cross (Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 512
      - Committee of Russian Zemstvos and Cities (Prince G. L'vov) (Folder 2)
      - International Committee of Young Men's Christian Associations (Folder 3)
      - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Fund
        - General
          - General (Folder 4)
          - Financial file (Folder 5-6)
            Available on microfilm reels 512 and 513
        - Bristol Disaster Committee (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 513
        - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Folder 8)
      - League of Nations (Box 439)
        - General (Folder 1-2)
        - High Commission for Russian Refugees (Fridtjof Nansen) (Folder 3)
      - Refugee Protection Committee (Folder 4)
      - Russian Refugee Mission (Folder 5)
      - Russkii Komitet v Turtsii (Folder 6)
      - Whittemore Relief Committee (Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (Folder 8)
      Available on microfilm reel 514
    - Evacuation file
      - Balkans (Serbia and Bulgaria) (Folder 9)
      - Canada (Folder 10)
      - France (Folder 11)
      - Philippines (Folder 12)
      - United States (Box 440)
        - General (Folder 1)
        - Russian Refugee Relief Society of America, Inc. (Folder 2)
    - Financial records (Folder 3-5)
    - Repatriation file (Folder 6)
    - Reports
      - General (Folder 7-8)
      - Students (Folder 9)
        Available on microfilm reel 515
- Russian Famine Relief, Inquiries File, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 515-526
  Inquiries from U.S. residents interested in sending aid to relatives in the Soviet Union and locating missing persons, and inquiries from residents of the Soviet Union looking for relatives in the U.S., arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - General
    - Insurance (Folder 10)
    - Mail (Folder 11)
    - Package shipments (Folder 12-13)
    - Relief organizations other than ARA (Box 441, Folder 1)
    - Withdrawal of ARA (Folder 2)
  - Inquiries from residents of the United States regarding individuals in the Soviet Union
    - Aid
      - General
        - A-B (Folder 3)
        - C-E (Folder 4)
          Available on microfilm reel 516
        - F (Folder 5)
        - G (Folder 6-7)
        - H (Box 442, Folder 1)
        - J (Folder 2)
        - K (Folder 3)
        - L (Folder 4)
        - M (Folder 5)
        - N (Folder 6)
        - O (Folder 7)
        - P (Folder 8)
          Available on microfilm reel 517
        - R (Box 443, Folder 1)
        - S (Folder 2-4)
          Available on microfilm reels 517 and 518
        - T-Z (Folder 5)
          Available on microfilm reel 518
      - Clothing
        - General (Folder 6)
        - A (Folder 7)
        - B (Folder 8)
        - C (Folder 9)
        - D (Folder 10)
          Available on microfilm reel 519
        - E (Box 444, Folder 1)
        - F (Folder 2)
        - G (Folder 3)
        - H (Folder 4)
        - I (Folder 5)
        - J (Folder 6)
        - K (Folder 7)
        - L (Folder 8)
        - M (Folder 9)
        - N (Folder 10)
        - O (Folder 11)
        - P (Folder 12)
        - R (Folder 13)
        - S (Folder 14)
        - T (Folder 15)
        - V (Folder 16)
        - W (Folder 17)
        - Z (Folder 18)
      - Food (Box 445)
        - A (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 520
        - B (Folder 2)
        - C (Folder 3)
        - D (Folder 4)
        - E (Folder 5)
        - F (Folder 6)
        - G (Folder 7)
        - H (Folder 8)
        - I-J (Folder 9)
        - K (Folder 10)
        - L (Folder 11)
        - M (Folder 12)
        - N-O (Folder 13)
        - P (Folder 14)
        - R (Folder 15)
        - S (Folder 16)
        - T (Folder 17)
        - U-Z (Folder 18)
    - Missing persons (Box 446)
      - General
        - A (Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 521
        - B (Folder 2)
        - C (Folder 3)
        - D (Folder 4-5)
        - E (Folder 6)
        - F (Folder 7)
        - K (Folder 8)
        - L (Folder 9)
          Available on microfilm reel 522
        - M (Folder 10)
        - N (Box 447, Folder 1)
        - O (Folder 2)
        - Q-R (Folder 3)
        - S (Folder 4-5)
          Available on microfilm reel 523
        - T (Folder 6)
        - U-V (Folder 7)
        - W-Z (Folder 8)
      - Lists sent to newspapers for publication (Folder 9)
    - Money transfer
      - General - Banks (Folder 10)
        Available on microfilm reel 524
      - A (Box 448, Folder 1)
      - B (Folder 2)
      - C (Folder 3)
      - D (Folder 4)
      - E-F (Folder 5)
        Available on microfilm reel 525
      - G (Folder 6)
      - H (Folder 7)
      - I-J (Folder 8)
      - K (Folder 9)
      - L (Folder 10)
      - M (Folder 11)
      - N (Box 449, Folder 1)
      - P (Folder 2)
      - R (Folder 3)
      - S (Folder 4-5)
      - T (Folder 6)
      - U-W (Folder 7)
      - Y-Z (Folder 8)
        Available on microfilm reel 526
  - Inquiries from residents of the Soviet Union re individuals residing in the United States (Folder 9-11)
- Russian Famine Relief, Medical Service File, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 526-538
  Correspondence, reports, and financial records re A.R.A. medical work in the Soviet Union, including records of the American Red Cross and the U.S. Army Surplus Program, arranged alphabetically by subject and by physical form thereunder.
  - General (Box 450)
    - Correspondence
      - General. Includes invoices, receipts and correspondence re purchase and delivery of supplies (Folder 1-2)
      - Letters of gratitude (Folder 3)
    - Reports
      - General
        - General. Addressed to President Warren G. Harding and administration officials re distribution of Army surplus medical supplies and supplies donated by the American Red Cross (Folder 4)
        - Consolidated report (Folder 5-6)
          Available on microfilm reels 526 and 527
        - Medical report, 1922 June-July (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 527
      - "History of the Medical Division of the ARA " Proofsheets, September, 1921 -June 1923. (Folder 8)
    - Subject file
      - Accountability (Folder 9)
      - Cholera (Folder 10)
        - William Bingham donations (Folder 11-12)
        - Rockefeller Memorial Gift (Folder 13)
      - Mothers' packages (Box 451, Folder 1)
      - Personnel
        - Applications
          - Administrators of medical supply (Folder 2)
          - Dentists (Folder 3)
          - Doctors
            - General
              - A-H (Folder 4)
              - I-P (Folder 5)
                Available on microfilm reel 528
              - Q-V (Folder 6)
              - W-Z (Folder 7)
            - Godfrey, E. (Folder 8)
            - Walsh, W. (Folder 9)
        - Correspondence (Box 452)
          - General (Folder 1-3)
          - Brink, Hobart (Folder 4)
          - Doty, S. (Folder 5)
          - Kares, E. (Folder 6)
          - La Salle, James (Folder 7)
          - Mulford, J. (Folder 8)
            Available on microfilm reel 529
          - Phillips, Ira (Folder 9)
      - Poisoning (Folder 10)
      - Publicity. Clippings (Folder 11)
      - Requisitions. Includes orders for medical supplies and hospital equipment (Folder 12)
      - Requisitions. Includes orders for medical supplies and hospital equipment (Box 453, Folder 1-8)
        Available on microfilm reels 529 and 530
      - Requisitions. Includes orders for medical supplies and hospital equipment (Box 454, Folder 1-5)
        Available on microfilm reels 530 and 531
      - Surplus - Storage (Folder 6)
        Available on microfilm reel 531
      - Typhus (Folder 7)
      - Vaccination of Soviet children (Folder 8)
  - American Red Cross (Box 455)
    - General. Includes correspondence, reports, accounts, and listings of shipments of medical supplies related to the Red Cross
      - General (Folder 1-2)
      - 1921
        - August (Folder 3)
        - September (Folder 4)
        - October (Folder 5)
        - November (Folder 6)
        - December (Folder 7)
      - 1922
        - January (Folder 8)
        - February (Folder 9)
        - March (Folder 10)
        - April (Folder 11)
          Available on microfilm reel 532
        - May-December (Folder 12)
      - 1923 (Folder 13)
    - Agreement between ARA and ARC (Box 456, Folder 1)
    - Appropriation of $3,000,000
      - Accounting of purchases and shipments (Folder 2)
      - Expenditures (Folder 3)
      - Liquidation account (Folder 4)
      - Revolving fund (Folder 5)
        Available on microfilm reel 533
      - Unexpended ballance (Folder 6)
    - Donations - Motor vehicles (Folder 7)
    - Personnel file - Salaries and allowances (Folder 8)
    - Reports
      - General
        - General. Final Report (Folder 9-11)
        - 1921 (Box 457)
          - September (Folder 1)
          - October (Folder 2)
          - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
        - 1922
          - January (Folder 5)
          - February (Folder 6)
          - March (Folder 7)
          - April-May (Folder 8)
            Available on microfilm reel 534
          - August-September (Folder 9)
          - October (Folder 10)
          - November-December (Folder 11)
      - Croce Rossa Italiana Comitato Centrale (Folder 12)
      - Deutsches Rotes Kreuz (Folder 13)
      - Missiia ukraïnskogo chervonogo khresta v zakhidnii evropi (Folder 14)
    - Requisitions
      - General (Folder 15-17)
      - General (Box 458, Folder 1-6)
        Available on microfilm reels 534 and 535
      - Liquidation (Folder 7)
        Available on microfilm reel 535
      - Summaries (Folder 8)
    - Stocks and supplies (Folder 9)
  - United States. Army - Surplus (Box 459)
    - General. Correspondence
      - New York Office
        - London
          - 1921 (Folder 1)
          - 1921-1922 (Folder 2)
          - 1922 (Folder 3)
          - 1923 (Folder 4)
            Available on microfilm reel 536
        - Moscow (Folder 5)
        - Riga (Folder 6)
      - Near East Relief (Folder 7)
      - Surgeon General's Office (Folder 8)
      - United States. Shipping Board (Folder 9)
      - Washington Office (Folder 10)
    - Accountability (Folder 11)
    - Authority to act given to Col. J. W. Krueger by Herbert Hoover (Folder 12)
    - Balance of surplus property (Folder 13)
    - Congressional appropriation (Folder 14)
    - Delivery of goods (Box 460)
      - Inspection and shipment
        - General (Folder 1)
        - Chloroform (Folder 2)
        - Markings and packing (Folder 3)
        - Narcotics, liquor and pistols (Folder 4)
        - Shirts and towels (Folder 5)
        - Surplus stock (Folder 6)
        - Unidentified cases (Folder 7)
          Available on microfilm reel 537
      - Railway transport (Folder 8)
      - Rates for storage, freight, insurance (Folder 9)
      - Shipping tickets (Folder 10)
      - Warehousing (Folder 11)
    - Depots
      - Germany - Coblenz (Folder 12)
      - United States
        - General (Folder 13)
        - Atlanta (Folder 14)
        - Boston (Folder 15)
        - Chicago (Folder 16)
        - New York - Brooklyn (Folder 17)
        - St. Louis (Box 461, Folder 1)
        - San Francisco (Folder 2)
        - Washington, D.C. (Folder 3)
    - Executive order, signed Warren G. Harding (Folder 4)
    - Insurance (Folder 5)
    - Senate Bill S 2708 (Folder 6)
- Russian Famine Relief, Press File, 1921-1923
  Available on microfilm reels 537-548
  Clippings, daily news summaries, abstracts and translations of foreign and domestic press related to the famine in the Soviet Union and A.R.A. activities, arranged alphabetically by physical form.
  - General
    - Baker, George Barr. Notes on Russia (Folder 7)
    - Garner, B., "Breaking the Famine" (Folder 8)
    - Wallace, John (Folder 9)
      Available on microfilm reel 538
  - Clippings, daily news summaries and abstracts. Includes English translations of foreign press
    - Baltic
      - General, 1921
        - April (Folder 10)
        - May (Folder 11)
        - June (Folder 12)
        - July (Folder 13)
        - August (Folder 14)
        - November-December (Folder 15)
      - Commercial extracts (Folder 16)
    - Czechoslovak (Box 462, Folder 1)
      Available on microfilm reel 539
    - Danish (Folder 2)
    - English
      - General (Folder 3-11)
        Available on microfilm reels 539 and 540
      - General (Box 463, Folder 1-7)
        Available on microfilm reels 540 and 541
      - Daily news summary (Box 464)
        - 1922
          - August-October (Folder 1)
            Available on microfilm reel 541
          - November-December (Folder 2)
        - 1923 (Folder 3)
          Available on microfilm reel 542
    - Estonian (Folder 4)
    - German. Includes Austrian (Folder 5)
    - Jewish
      - General
        - General. Includes correspondence with the Jewish Correspondence Bureau and editors of Jewish newspapers (Folder 6)
        - Digest of news and comment in Yiddish press (Folder 7)
        - Translations and clippings of the International Jewish Press Bureau Inc. (Folder 8)
      - Day (Box 465, Folder 1)
        Available on microfilm reel 543
      - Forward (Folder 2)
      - "Idgeskom" (Folder 3)
      - Jewish Daily News (Folder 4)
      - Jewish Spectator (Folder 5)
      - Jewish Tribune (Folder 6)
      - Jewish World (Folder 7)
    - Latvian (Folder 8-9)
    - Russian
      - General
        - General
          - General (Folder 10)
          - 1920-1921 (Folder 11)
          - 1921 (Folder 12-13)
          - 1922 (Folder 14)
            Available on microfilm reel 544
          - 1922 (Box 466, Folder 1-4)
          - 1923 (Folder 5-8)
            Available on microfilm reels 544 and 545
        - Moscow press (Box 467, Folder 1)
          Available on microfilm reel 545
        - Russian Trade Delegation, London. Bulletins (Folder 2)
      - Izvestiia (Folder 3-4)
      - Russian Information and Review
        - 1921 (Folder 7)
        - 1922 (Folder 8-9)
          Available on microfilm reel 546
        - 1923 (Box 468, Folder 1-4)
          Available on microfilm reels 546 and 547
        - 1924 (Folder 5)
          Available on microfilm reel 547
    - Russian, Baltic and Polish
      - General (Folder 6)
      - 1921 (Folder 7)
    - Ukrainian (Folder 8)